

#### **ABOUT ME**

Full stack developer with over 4 years of programming experience. Solid professional and academic background in Cyber Security. With an in-depth knowledge on both programming and security principles, I have developed a comprehensive skill set. Handson experience in leading and conducting security assessments. Proficient in front and back-end coding languages, such as Python, React.JS, TypeScript, Swift, Java, Django, and more. Newfound passion for blockchain technology, currently learning with a desire to grow in this rapidly evolving space.

#### **EDUCATION**

## **University of Warwick**

2017 - 2018

MSc. Cybersecurity and Management

Distinction

Dissertation on "Applying Machine Learning to Automate Detection and Mitigation Processes for On-Going Ransomware Attacks on Windows Environments.".

https://github.com/ShahNami/Dissertation

## **University College Howest**

2013 - 2016

BSc. Applied Computer Science and Cybercrime

First-Class

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### **F-Secure Consulting** (previously MWR InfoSecurity)

2019 - present

• Open-Source intelligence service development.

**Cybersecurity Consultant** 

- Internal tool development.
  - Bucket Modular Python web scraper for bulk domain parsing and categorising into collections.
  - Impulse Dockerised and secured calendar manager used to automate the import of events into MacOS.
  - Sn0int (module) Rust and Python script to bridge commands from the Rust sandbox to the host system.

- Conducted research on the Handshake (HNS) blockchain protocol.
- Infrastructure, mobile and web application testing.
- Led and trained associate consultants to deliver external asset mapping assessments.

# **App Maven Limited**

2019 - present

**Software Engineer** 

- Web and Mobile application development (React, TypeScript, Django, React-Native, Swift, Java / Kotlin).
- Setup and deployed a validator node for the Monet blockchain network.
- Participant in the Mosaic Networks Hackathon
  - Pong 2.0 Android Peer to Peer game using Babble as the underlying consensus.
- Developed in Ethereum's Solidity.
  - Familiarised with the Ganache framework and Truffle client.
  - o Deployed a yield farming smart contract.
- Manage finances, legal and client relationships.

# The Security Factory

2017

Web application penetration testing.

**Penetration Tester** 

- Developed an SSL Scan output aggregator (Python).
- Automated and manual vulnerability analysis using BurpSuite, Nessus, Nmap, OWASP methodologies, and more.

**Accenture** 2016 - 2017

Shadowed security assessments.

**Security Implementation** 

Developed and organized a city-wide CTF.

**Services Associate** 

- Consolidated Bills of Materials.
- Reviewed and documented Nagios configurations.

# CONTACT

Portfolio <a href="mailto:nami.sh">nami.sh</a>
LinkedIn <a href="mailto:linkedin.com/in/namis">linkedin.com/in/namis</a>
Email <a href="mailto:me@nami.sh">me@nami.sh</a>
GitHub <a href="mailto:github.com/ShahNami">github.com/ShahNami</a>
References <a href="mailto:on/request">on request</a>